paperpkads.com 2015-05-26

# Privacy Policy of Paperpk.com

### Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

The Information We Collect 

The following notice (items 1-3) applies to all information collected or submitted on the Accountingformanagement.com website. 

**Emailing a friend about our website**  
On some pages we allow you to email a friend who might be interested in certain pages of our website. We ask you to supply your email address so when your friend wants to reply to the email, the reply comes to you, and not to us. We do not store any email addresses, and your email address will simply be gone after the program has finished the procedure, and you see the final page. We do store your email address in a cookie on your computer. If you ever use the service again, we'll "know" your email address and name, and you don't have to fill out those lines anymore.(When you subscribe to some service then your email address is stored and can be used to send other offers or marketing email from our company or third party) 

**Tracking and statistics**  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

**Google AdSense and cookies**  
We use Google AdSense to supply our visitors with relevant advertisements throughout our website. Google uses cookies in order to make these ads more relevant to our visitors. [Learn more about cookies and how to opt-out of them](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) 

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Changes in this privacy statement 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please [contact us](http://www.paperpk.com/contact-us.php)
